Hello everyone! I'm Suzuka Tomita from Hinatazaka46!
Today is a collaboration between Car Prime and Hinatazaka Channel.
I'm going to do drifting at a circuit!
From now on...
It's about 5:20 in the morning.
On this side of the Hinatasaka Channel
I'm going to be following closely.
I'll be with this video all day today.
Please enjoy it along with Car Prime's video.
GO!
I was kind of nervous, so I probably didn't get much sleep today.
That's right.
It's my first time.
It's my first time driving a manual transmission.
I wonder if I can do it.
I've recently started practicing driving by myself.
I've always driven with my mom, but...
I used to drive for about an hour each way.
It's a lot of fun.
I'm more nervous when I'm alone.
I have to do the navigation by myself.
I also have to take members of the group with me.
One step closer.
Flav?
I'm going to flive.
I want to flive.
Flutter, flutter, flutter, flutter, flutter, flutter, flutter, flutter, flutter, flutter...
I've changed into my racing suit.
This is a newly made racing suit!
I've watched a lot of videos on drifting and how to drive a manual car.
I've watched a lot of videos on how to drive a manual car.
I hope to be able to do that!
The points I'm particular about are
The point of particularity is the logo of all of you that we have stuffed under the fingernails!
This is really, really important.
I heard that it is very rare to see the logos of Honda and Toyota on a racing suit.
This is the logo of Super Formula and this is the sponsor's logo.
And this is the sponsor's logo.
It's made by a company called Sparco.
This is the logo of “Let's meet at the circuit” by ABEMA, and the logo of “Hinatazaka
And the logo of Hinatazaka.
Purple is my penlight color.
I wanted to make it with purple as a precious color, and this is my Jimny Sierra.
I used the green color of my Jimmy Sierra as an accent color.
I put my name here.
That's about it.
Okay, let's go to the car that we're going to use today, shall we?
I'd like to go see the car we're going to use today.
It's a beautiful day for a drive.
Perfect day for a drive.
So there's more than the sea.
Here's the car we're going to use today.
This is the car we're going to use today.
Toyota's
GR86
We are going to use it!
It's so cool!
I'm so excited!
I'm totally looking forward to it.
I've never driven much.
I've never been in a sport before.
That's it!
I went to see the second YouTube video.
I went to see.
I went to see sports cars and SUVs.
This is the car that I also saw in the second YouTube episode.
So today, I'd like to show you
I'd like to try drifting this car with you.
I'd like to try drifting with you.
How many cars do you have now?
Twenty cars.
Twenty?
Not only nice cars, but also various light cars.
If I had all of them, I would have 20 cars.
I have a lot of cars.
One car.
You bought one, didn't you?
You recently took delivery of a car
We met for a few minutes.
It's only been five minutes.
I've only overheard a little bit about it.
He has an automatic transmission license.
So?
I've never driven a manual.
And yet?
And yet today he's going to drift in a manual.
Can you do it?
I don't think so.
That's what I thought, too.
But everyone said...
If you teach me how to do it, I'm sure I can do it.
I'm sure I can do it.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
That's why he changed the tires today.
I'll do it. I'll do it.
He said he's not that naive...
You're right. - You're right.
- It's not that sweet! - What?
- What? - What?
- What? What? I'll help you use it today. - What?
- What? - I brought it.
- I brought it! - I brought it!
- I brought it! - What? What? Can I have it?
- And wait, it's purple, right? - Isn't it perfect?
- Isn't it perfect? - Isn't it perfect?
- It's my member's color, or rather, my natural color is purple, and this one is purple too.
That's great! Thank you!
Member color?
Member color.
Can I say something about member colors?
Yes, sir.
In this industry, I'm the current member of the group, and I'm in charge of Murazaki, right?
In our industry, a car has a member's name, and when Ember says she's going to play...
From Rollator to member... that way.
Only a car enthusiast would understand... but I think you get the idea.
If the title is “Drift Challenge Today,” I'll give it a shot.
What's the title of the challenge?
If it's about drifting, I don't think it's possible.
What percentage is impossible?
95% impossible.
That much?
Well, first of all, today's location is only half a day, right?
Half an hour.
That's right, I can't do it.
I don't think I'm going to be drifting today. I think I'm going to be driving a manual transmission car.
Here's today's car.
Toyota 86.
It's a manual
State what you know about manuals.
There's a clutch.
There's the RPMs.
It has everything.
There's a six-speed, which is in every, uh...
Uh, there's a six-speed.
Uh, but it depends on the car.
Uh-huh.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Okay, bye.
When you let off the clutch.
I have to raise the engine rpm
I'm gonna have to rev the engine a little bit.
Just a little bit. You have to step on the gas a little bit to do it.
You have to step on the gas pedal a little bit.
I'm going to step on the clutch.
What does it mean to step on the clutch?
There's the engine, which is the mass.
And here is the transmission.
And then there's what we call the gears.
I'm going to make it transparent.
Engine
The engine is the power output, and the gears are the drive, or the gears that make the car go,
So the gears and the engine are separated.
When you step on the clutch, you have released it.
The engine and transmission are separated.
You put it in gear at that point, because now you're stepping on the clutch.
When the clutch stands on the engine revs and the transmission revs, it's disengaged.
By releasing the pedal like this, the clutch comes closer and closer to the transmission.
The clutch moves closer to the transmission.
The power of the engine is transmitted to the gears.
The gears turn the tires and the car moves forward.
The engine speed has to be increased a little bit.
Like turning.
When the clutch is released while the engine is revved up a little bit, the clutch is connected.
I have the image of this backwards, but if I can explain it simply, it would be really great if I could do it.
I've never put in a second gear, but you can do a low limit.
It could be super internet news.
I'm not sure if it's 100% doable or not.
But you know what?
It would be really cool if you could do it.
This Power Prime project is a big collaboration with a certain person.
A big collaboration with a certain person.
I'd like to invite you to join us right away.
I'm looking forward to working with you soon.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Suzuka Tomita, from Minazuka46.
I look forward to working with you.
So I'd like to go.
I'm going to put it in gear 1. Is that okay?
You can put it in.
Like this? Voice in the car won't stall.
At first, it's like starting off.
I was using my left foot.
The moment I changed my technique.
It started to stall.
I was putting my heel on the clutch.
I was stepping on the clutch
I could get it right.
I like the old way better.
It's better in the old days.
It's better to float
The second half of the race gets more intense, so the sound in the car, the sound in the car, the sound in the car
Sound in the car
Voice in the car
Well, I'd like to turn around now.
I'm off. Yes!
One shot?
One shot? That's great.
That's great!
I'm so happy.
I'm glad Curry chased you.
I'm glad you were chased by the curry.
I can't do it, so I'm not being chased.
I don't want to be chased by curry because I can't do it.
I turned him down at the end.
I think I'm more confident about Straht.
I'm more confident.
It's more rewarding.
I'm not a good communicator, but it's great that you were able to get around at that level.
But I'm really happy for you. It was fun.
It was really fun.
But I'm not going to lie, it's really fun to drive.
If you do this a little more, your left foot will become friends with the clutch.
That's right. Even today, it only took me two and a half hours.
Just, you know, bend it one more time.
Wait a minute.
It's too close.
You're practicing your launch.
Thank you.
Yes, sir. How did it go?
I'm ready to launch.
Okay, let's go to the restricted area.
It's true, after all this time.
The hurdle for the limited edition manual is much lower than it used to be.
It's a lot lower than it used to be, isn't it?
I'm not going to get my license tomorrow or with a manual.
So today, I did a video in collaboration with Car Prime.
I tried drifting!
It was my first time to drive a manual car.
It was really hard to start the car.
I can still do drifting much better without having to do it many times.
I tried it a few times and it was like I could do it if I tried.
It was really difficult to start the car.
Mr. Taniguchi's advice really helped me a lot.
Taniguchi's advice was really easy to understand without having to chew it up in my mind.
It was easy to understand.
Thanks to your advice
I didn't think I could succeed in drifting so quickly.
I'm a little more surprised.
I'm really about 80%, 92%.
I'm not sure if I'll be able to do it today.
We were talking about it at the beginning.
I thought that today's result would give me a lot of confidence for the future, and above all, it was a lot of fun and made me fall in love with cars even more.
Above all, it was a lot of fun and made me fall in love with cars even more!
I can't wait to see what everyone thinks after watching this video.
I'm really looking forward to seeing what you all think of this video!
I'm really looking forward to seeing what you all think of the video!
I hope you will check out the video and enjoy it as much as I did.
I hope you enjoy the video as much as I did.
See you soon.